&GT；&GT；凯尔·辛普森：我会说，就像其他所有的手术一样，
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: And I would claim that just like every other operation,
如果您了解这些类型是什么，这是很有帮助的。
it is helpful if you understand what the types are.
就像其他的手术一样，你必须问问自己，
Like every other operation, you have to ask yourself,
如果我知道类型，这里的强制有没有帮助？
if I know the types, is coercion here helpful or not?
也许它有帮助，也许它不是。
Maybe it is helpful, maybe it isn't.
这是一个批判性的分析。
It's a critical analysis.
它将讨论从双等分转移到坏的和不可预测的
It shifts the discussion away from double equals is bad and unpredictable
我是想允许强制比较还是不想允许？
to do I wanna allow a coercive comparison or do I not wanna allow that?
在这种情况下，这样做对我更有帮助还是
In this particular case, is it more helpful to me to do so or
是不是没那么有用了？
is it less helpful?
是更安全还是更不安全？
Is it more safe or is it less safe?
换句话说，你需要是批判性的，分析性的思想家，并且
In other words, you need to be critical, analytical thinkers, and
看看你的代码。
look at your code.
并决定关于代码你可以知道什么，不能知道什么。
And decide what you can know about your code and what you can't.
本质上是关于双等和三等的决定
And essentially the decision about double equals and triple equals
是一个尾随指示器，表明您是否真正理解了您的程序。
is a trailing indicator of whether you actually understand your program.
让我再说一遍。
Let me say that again.
你选择使用三等号，不仅仅是因为
Your choice to use triple equals, it's not just because
有些人在一本书中写道，你应该永远使用三倍等于。
some guy wrote in a book that you should always use triple equals.
您实际选择使用三重等于是一个指向后的尾随指示符
Your actual choice to use triple equals is a trailing indicator which points back
事实上，你不知道关于比较中的类型的一些事情，所以
to the fact that you don't know something about the types in that comparison and so
你必须保护自己。
you have to protect yourself.
我的观点是，如果可能的话，也许修复根部会更好
And my opinion is, if at all possible, maybe it would be better to fix the root
问题是，我不知道在这个比较中的类型是什么。
problem, which is that I don't know what the types are in this comparison.
它太不可预测了，它太多态了。
It's too unpredictable, it's too polymorphic.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：这将导致更好的代码和更少的bug，
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: That's gonna lead to better code with fewer bugs,
无论您使用的是双等号还是三等号。
regardless of whether you use a double equals or a triple equals.
决定你的类型，让那些类型变得显而易见。
Deciding what your types are, making it obvious what those are.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：那么我们知道那些类型吗？
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: So do we know those types?
让我们来看一下双等号将会做什么
Let's take a look at what the double equals is going to do
如果类型不同。
if the types are different.
首先，如果任何一方的类型为空或未定义，
First off, if the types are null or undefined on either side,
这就是这两个子句配对的意思，如果x为NULL，y为未定义或
that's what these two clauses are paired to say, if x is null and y is undefined or
反之亦然，然后返回true。
a vice versa, then return true.
换句话说，NO值和未定义的值强制等于
In other words, the no value and the undefined value are coercively equal to
相互之间，而不是语言中的其他值，这就是第10条所说的。
each other and to no other values in the language, which is what clause 10 says.
它说返回错误。
It says return false.
NULL和UNDEFINED将不匹配此算法中的任何其他子句，
Null and undefined will not match any other clauses in this algorithm,
第2及3条除外。
other than clause 2 and 3.
所以这只是对彼此的强制。
And so it's only coercive to each other.
我发现这是关于JavaScript的一个非常有用的事实，因为，
I find that to be a tremendously useful fact about JavaScript because,
老实说，我不喜欢有两个空值。
quite honestly, I don't like having two empty values.
我觉得这很令人困惑。
I find that to be confusing.
所以我更愿意处理一个空值。
So I would much rather deal with one empty value.
并且由于NULL的类型比未定义的短，
And since null is shorter to type than undefined,
我宁愿处处都是空的。
I'd rather deal with null everywhere.
并尽可能假装未定义的不存在。
And pretend as much as possible that undefined doesn't exist.
或者至少假装它们是可以互换的。
Or at least pretend that they're interchangeable.
JavaScript确实在它们之间做了一些区别，
JavaScript does make some distinctions between them,
例如默认值算法。
such as the default value algorithm.
但是，在大多数情况下，您可以选择处理null和
But, for the most part, you have the option of treating null and
未被定义为通过强制平等无法区分。
undefined as indistinguishable through coercive equality.
所以你可以做这样的检查，你可以有一个工作坊
So you could do a check like this, you could have a workshop one and
第二个工作坊，那里有一个主题属性。
a workshop two, and there's a topic property on there.
如果设置了Topic属性并且它为NULL，则可以询问该属性，或者
You could be asking of that topic property if it's been set and it's null, or
如果它从来没有被设置过，或者如果它已经被设置了，并且它太没有定义。
if it's never been set at all, or if it's been set and it's too undefined.
你可以试着区分这两个，但是
You could try to distinguish between those two, but
我认为在几乎所有情况下，这都不是一个有用的区别。
I would argue in almost all cases, that's not a useful distinction.
属性是否曾经创建并已重置回NULL，或者
Whether the property was ever created and has been reset back to null, or
无论它是否被重置回未定义，或者它是否从未被创建过。
whether it's been reset back to undefined, or whether it was never created at all.
这些基本上都是相同的条件，或者至少我认为，
Those are basically all the same condition, or at least I would argue,
这是一种更好的编码方式，可以将它们视为不可区分的。
that's a better way to code, to treat those as indistinguishable.
所以对你来说一种选择是在第五行写下你所做的
So one option is for you to write what you do on lines five and
六，也就是使用这个三重相等，它不允许强制和
six, which is to use this triple equals that does not allow coercion and
明确检查所有这些情况。
explicitly checks all of those cases.
显式检查workshop1.topic是否为null或
Explicitly checks that workshop1.topic is null or
workshop1.topic未定义，workshop2主题也是如此。
workshop1.topic is undefined and the same thing is true of workshop2 topic.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：通过这里的显式表达，您是否获得了任何可读性方面的好处？
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Are you gaining anything readability-wise by being explicit here?
问问自己，读者是否从杂耍中获益
Ask yourself the question if the reader has benefited from having to juggle
在他们的头脑中，两个空洞的价值观之间的区别是什么？
in their head the distinction between two empty values?
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：我的断言是没有，他们没有受益。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: My assertion is that no, they are not benefited.
然后使用双等号，就像我们在第12行和第13行做的那样，
And using the double equals like we do down here on lines 12 and 13,
更清楚了。
it's far more clear.
它说，无论是空的还是未定义的，告诉我它们是否是空的。
It says, whether are null or undefined, tell me if they're empty or not.
告诉我它们是否是这两个空值中的一个。
Tell me if they're one of those two empty values.
顺便说一句，我只是选了两个中较短的，因为它打字较少。
And by the way, I just picked the shorter of the two cuz it's less to type.
凯尔·辛普森：好吗？
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Okay?
这是一个使用强制相等的示例，并且
This is an example of using coercive equality, and
即使是一些对胁迫最严厉的批评者，
even some of the staunchest harshest critics of coercion,
您会发现他们在代码中使用双等于空检查。
you will find them using double equals null checks in their code.
因为它比其他一些双等号的用法争议性更小。
Because it's less controversial than some of the other double equals usages.
大多数人似乎对此没意见。
Most people seem to be okay with that.
尽管JFLint说不，但大多数其他人都打开了这些连接规则。
Even though JFLint says no no, most other people have those linting rules turned on.
我使用ESLint，它是一个令人惊讶的可配置的Linter。
I use ESLint, it's an amazingly configurable linter.
我有一套和你完全不同的规则，我确定，
I have a very different rule set than you do, I'm sure,
因为我有非常不同的观点，但我使用ESLint工具
cuz I have very different opinions, but I use an ESLint tool and
我打开了哪些规则帮助我编写更好的代码，这就是linters的用途。
I turn on what rules help me write better code and that's what linters are for.
linters是一种帮助您决定是否或
Linters are an opinion that helps you decide whether or
您的代码不是以这样的方式格式化的，或者是以这样的方式构造的，
not your code is formatted in such a way where, or structured in such a way,
以避免bug或是否可能发生问题。
to avoid bugs or whether it's likely that a problem will occur.
它不是检查你的程序是否正确。
It's not checking if your programming is correct.
它给你一个关于你是否做了正确的事情的意见。
It's giving you an opinion on whether you've done the right thing.
关于观点的问题是每个人都有不同的观点。
The thing about opinions is that everybody's got different opinions.
所以最好的工具是那些最可配置的工具，
So the best tools are the ones that are most configurable,
不只是个人意见，而是对团队最有效的。
not just to individual opinions, but most effectively for teams.
让团队决定什么对他们有效。
Let a team decide what is effective for them.
在任何程度上，您使用的工具与共享对您的代码的意见
To any extent that you use a tool that shares an opinion about your code with
您，通过错误地确定您的构建过程，达到该工具的程度
you, by way of erroring out your build process, to the extent that that tool is
无法对其进行配置，以便您可以更有效地完成工作，
unable for you to configure it so that you can get your job done more effectively and
它迫使你改变你的编码方式来适应它，
it forces you to change the way you code to adapt to it,
那么这个工具对你没有帮助，它是在阻碍你的发展机会。
then that tool is not helping you, it is hampering your development opportunities.
如果它不够聪明，不能理解它在做什么。
If it's not smart enough to understand what it's doing.
例如，我使用ESLint，ESLint有一系列非常棒的规则，
For example, I use ESLint and ESLint's got a bunch of really great rules in,
但它有一些很幼稚的规则。
but it's got some rules which are pretty naive.
其中一个规则必须处理变量声明，
One of those rules has to deal with variable declarations,
是否允许您在作用域的早期使用变量声明。
whether you're allowed to use a variable declaration earlier in the scope.
现在我可以清楚地说，我们将在我们单位的范围内回到这一点，
Now I can clearly say, and we're gonna come back to this in our unit on scope,
但我可以清楚地告诉你，我不建议说A等于2
but I can clearly say to you that I wouldn't recommend saying A equals two and
然后是Var A，这是一个糟糕的用法。
then Var A, that's a terrible usage of that.
但是同样的规则阻止了这一点，也阻止了我说A等于2
But that same rule that prevents that also prevents me from saying A equals two
如果var A不在代码中的函数上方，则在函数内部。
inside of a function if the var A isn't above the function in the code.
这完全不是一回事，但是这个工具根本不够聪明
That's not at all the same thing, but that tool is not at all smart enough to
区分作用域行为中的这两个差异。
distinguish those two differences in scoping behavior.
这条规则阻碍了我，而不是帮助我。
And that rule gets in my way instead of helping me.
所以我不用那个规则。
So I don't use that rule.
关于ESLint的好消息是您可以编写自己的规则。
Good news about ESLint is you can write your own rules.
实际上，我刚刚编写了我的第一个ESLint规则插件。
I actually just wrote my first ESLint rule plug in.
我们稍后会在课程中讨论这个问题。
We'll talk about that one a bit later on the course.